# **APISIT KRUTSRI**

## Software Developer

(+66) 834117377 • Khlong San district, Bangkok, Thailand k.apisit@outlook.com • https://github.com/Apisit-Krutsri • www.linkedin.com/in/apisit-krutsri

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I work with a team for developing a web application project using MERN stack in bootcamp by Generation Thailand and with my problem solving skills and user centric mindset of my prior experience as an IT support and network engineer, I am confident I have the potential to be an effective team member and meet the objectives of Software Developer position.

#### **TECH SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6
- Tailwind CSS, MUI, React
- Express, Node.js, REST API
- MongoDB, SQL
- Git (GitHub)
- Linux
- Agile/Scrum

#### **PROJECT**

#### Foot-feet-for-fire

(September 2022 - December 2022)

Generation Thailand program

- Web application for exercise tracker for creating a new account, editing a profile and CRUD operations for activity cards to be represented on the dashboard.
- Built with MongoDB as database, React as frontend, Express and Node.js as backend for deploying to cloud.
- Collaborated with a team of 5 members to plan and operate for project accomplishment.

#### Network infrastructure enhancement in the customer's warehouse

(End of the year 2018)

V Outlook Solutions Co., Ltd.

- Increase network traffic capacity and high availability connection between 2 warehouses.
- Coordinated, Planned and documented to achieve the project requirements.
- Implemented network device configuration and installation for replacement operation.

#### The study of convolutional code efficiency

(Semester 1 2015 - Semester summer 2016)

Naresuan University

• Studied the efficiency of convolutional code (error correction coding) by decoding with Viterbi algorithm using MATLAB.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Junior software developer Bootcamp Cohort 3

(September 2022 - December 2022)

Generation Thailand program

- Learned technical skills in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, Node.js and MongoDB.
- Learned behavioral skills and mindsets to be a successful software developer.
- The final project was a web application exercise tracker with MERN stack.

# IT Support Technician

(July 2020 - July 2022)

Creative Economy Agency (Public Organization) · Contract

- Advised and resolved tickets to succeed the need of users.
- Provisioned Linux and Windows server virtual machines on VMware ESXi as supervisor's requirement.

# Network Engineer

(May 2018 - August 2019)

V Outlook Solutions Co., Ltd · Full-time

- Designed and implemented networking solutions to succeed in customer's requirements.
- Advised and resolved the customer's tickets to eliminate difficulty away from the customer.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Electrical Engineering**

(June 2012 - July 2017)

Naresuan University

• Bachelor's project: The study of convolutional code efficiency.

## **INTERESTS**

- Coding challenges for fun to figure out the better solution for coding and problem solving.
- Automation tools that make the working process faster, easier and better